[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "What do the five rings on the Olympic symbol represent?",
    "options": [
      "the five oceans",
      "the five continents",
      "the five planets",
      "five Greek Gods"
    ],
    "answer": "the five continents"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "The five rings of the Olympic symbol are in five different colours. Red, Green, Yellow, Blue and _______",
    "options": [
      "indigo",
      "violet",
      "orange",
      "black"
    ],
    "answer": "black"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "Olympic games were held in ancient Greece in the honour of Greek God ________",
    "options": [
      "zeus",
      "uranus",
      "apollo",
      "jupiter"
    ],
    "answer": "zeus"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "At which of the following cities have the Olympic games NOT been held twice?",
    "options": [
      "athens",
      "paris",
      "london",
      "atlanta"
    ],
    "answer": "atlanta"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "In which year were the first modern Olympic Games held?",
    "options": [
      "1900",
      "1896",
      "1904",
      "1892"
    ],
    "answer": "1896"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "Which of the following countries won the maximum number of medals at the first Olympic Games in 1896?",
    "options": [
      "Germany",
      "Great Britain",
      "USA",
      "Greece"
    ],
    "answer": "Greece"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "Which language other than English is the Official language of the International Olympic Committee?",
    "options": [
      "chinese",
      "french",
      "spanish",
      "german"
    ],
    "answer": "french"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "According to the Olympic charter, the duration of the competitions of the Olympic Games shall not exceed -",
    "options": [
      "20 days",
      "15 days",
      "12 days",
      "16 days"
    ],
    "answer": "16 days"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "At which of the following Olympics were gold medals made of pure gold last awarded?",
    "options": [
      "1912",
      "1920",
      "1936",
      "1948"
    ],
    "answer": "1912"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "Who of the following athletes has won the maximum number of individual gold medals at a single Olympics?",
    "options": [
      "mark sptiz",
      "michael phelps",
      "carl lewis",
      "matt biondi"
    ],
    "answer": "michael phelps"
  }
]